What are
you doing here?
I'm here to give
you a chance, Ted.
Come back
to the Eagles.
All you have
to do is
apologize
right here
in front
of everyone.
And maybe
I'll let you
crawl back and
be my
assistant coach.
Who the hell do
you think you are?
You want our
head coach to
apologize to you?
-Huh?
-Hey.
Whoa.
West is the head
coach of the Eagles.
Ted is
just a fired loser.
Giving him
his job again
would be charity.
He should
be thanking us.
I'm not
going back.
Don't tell me
you actually think
you can
win on your own.
Guys like you,
born at the bottom,
don't get to be
champions ever.
She's right.
Trash, like you,
belongs on
a trash team.
Like the Knights.
What is this?
Still chasing dreams
in your thirties?
Football is
a rich man's game.
One of our players
could buy your
whole damn team.
You'll never beat us.
Hey!
I'll say it
one last time.
I'll never
join the Eagles.
Oh, right,
you're doing
this for the raise.
Right?
Fine.
Uh...
How about five hundred
more a month?
That's what you
want, right?
You should
take it, Ted.
With that five hundred,
maybe you can
finally pay your
damn utility bills.
Five hundred?
Is that
all you've got?
Pathetic.
Mr. Vincent.
Here's your bonus
for leading
the Knights to victory.
Three million dollars.